Bold text.
Italic text.
Underlined text.
Times New Roman.
72px font size.
(Font size must be more than double the style's size to take affect.)
Diagonally moving subtitles.
(Unfortunately, YouTube's subtitle FPS is very poor,
thus it is very jittery when it comes to movement.)
Red font.
48px font size, with vertical movement.
Secondary style with preset configuration.
Basic karaoke timing.
Basic fade with 200ms in/out.
Vertical text. This gets interesting.
Shaking subtitles.
Chromatic aberration.
Glitching karaoke for your viewing pleasure.
Packed text.
Many
subtitles
all
at
once!
!!!
Subscript text.
Superscript text.
Custom text background and colour.
Unfortunately, there is no rotation/rotation animation
that is available to be used at the moment.
You will have to live with unicode upside-down characters.
Gradual font size increase to 72px.
Yellow subtitles fading to cyan in a 2000ms timespan.
Can't think of anything else to display. Hope this helped!
.ASS and .VTT files are available to download in desc.